

p: 678.451.7358

swhutchison(at)gmail.com

a: Marietta, GA 30062

house-of-wonder.com

Statement

I deliver. Every project is exciting, boring, a challenge, something beautiful, something ugly, a limitation and a possibility.

Skills

I design in Photoshop / Illustrator and hand code websites using HTML, CSS, Javascript, JQUERY, XML, PHP, MYSQL, RSS feeds, Flash, and/or whatever it takes to get the job done. I'm familiar with enterprise content management systems, Wordpress, best SEO practices, Web Standards, accessibility issues and information architecture. I've been working on the web since 2001.

Experience

Southern Company & Georgia Power // 2008 to present

I am a senior and lead designer/developer at Georgia Power and Southern Company. I'm involved in all phases of the design process from initial meetings with clients to designing comps to hand coding deliverables.

Cleveland.com // 4/2006 - 12/2007

Cleveland.com is the online presence of The Plain Dealer, Cleveland, Ohio's, daily newspaper and The Sun News, a collection of Cleveland's community newspapers. Cleveland.com is a subsidiary of Advance Internet. While at Cleveland.com I cleaned up a lot of old, clunky code, redesigned pages with beautiful CSS, designed a hundred or so animated GIFs for advertisers, and performed any maintenance or troubleshooting as necessary.

Sun News // 2005 - 2006

The Sun News is a collection of community newspapers in Clevelanc, OH. I worked as an illustrator creating creating maps and other graphic elements to accompany stories.

Cincinnati Citysearch // 2001

I was an Assistant Editor at CincinnatiCitysearch.com. At Citysearch I learned HTML. My duties included, writing stories, coding the stories, contributing photography, organizing campaigns, hiring and directing freelancers, editing story submissions, and working with local, regional and national editors.

Education

Associate's Degree Visual Communication & Design, Cuyahoga Community College, 2006

BA English Literature & Journalism, University of Cincinnati, 2001